You can't fit in when you already stand out.
Camp is a comedy, music, drama film directed by Todd Graff.
Misfits in their lives back home, a group of young
people live it up at musical-theater camp.
While the sports counselor is completely ignored, the kids' spend all their time in
rehearsal for a grueling schedule that involves a new show every two weeks.
Several personal stories come to the fore.
Vlad Baumann, played by Daniel Letterle.
Ellen Lucas, played by Joanna Chilcoat.
Michael Flores, played by Robin de Jesús.
Jenna Malloran, played by Tiffany Taylor.
Jill Simmons, played by Alana Allen.
Fritzi Wagner, played by Anna Kendrick.
Camp is a 2003 American musical comedy drama film written and directed by Todd
Graff about an upstate New York performing arts summer camp.
The film is based on Graff's own experiences at a similar camp called
Stagedoor Manor, where many scenes of the film were filmed.
Camp was released in the United States on July 25, 2003, by IFC Films.
The film received generally positive reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of summer camp, musical, coming of age, lgbt.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.